cleeng.com 2014-12-21

# Cleeng Privacy Policy - Cleeng

**IMPORTANT – PLEASE READ CAREFULY**

Cleeng believes that your privacy is very important. Cleeng respects the privacy of all the Users and Publishers of the Cleeng Service and all data and personal information provided by a User or Publisher will be treated as confidential. WE WILL NEVER SELL YOUR DATA TO THIRD PARTIES and our business model is not direct marketing. The information we collect is solely used for operating and improving our process and the Cleeng services.

Our Privacy policy is based on the following principles:

**1- Right to update, change or remove data**

Changing or removing personal information is possible via Your Cleeng Account and/or the Publisher Dashboard. Please note that certain information cannot be removed due to its necessity for the Cleeng Service and/or administration responsibilities of Cleeng. You are at all times entitled to change your personal information.

**2- Restricted use of information and cookies**

Other than the information you have provided to Cleeng, Cleeng also stores certain information for the use of the Cleeng Service, administration and the billing and remuneration process. This information includes: your I.P. address, accessed and/or sold content, referrals, votes and other actions you have made using the Cleeng Service. To store some of this information Cleeng makes use of cookies. Information stored by Cleeng will not be traced back to a personal User or Publisher other than is needed for administrative purposes and the billing and remuneration process. Cleeng does not allow third-party cookies to recognize your personal information.

**3- Never sell customer data**

Cleeng WILL NOT SELL your personal information and data to any third party. We also don’t sell or share user data for marketing purpose. Personal data will only be made available to a third party if, and in so far as, is needed for providing you with, or for improving, the Cleeng Service. At the present time, Cleeng may share your personal information with Ayden B.V. (Payment Processing Service) and/or Paypal if, and in so far as, this is needed for the correct completion of the payment process. This information can include: user name, last name, registered email, purchase date, price of the item bought. Cleeng may also share certain personal information with Publishers in order for them the best deliver their service to you. This information can include: username, purchase date, content ID purchased, registered email and purchase price.  
Third parties are at all times obliged to respect the confidentiality of your personal information and data. Third parties are not allowed make use of your data for marketing purposes except if you have explicitly authorized them to do so.

**4- Clear opt-in policy**

Only if you have permitted Cleeng to use your personal information to inform you about the Cleeng Service or otherwise Cleeng is allowed to do so. If you no longer wish to be informed by Cleeng, either you can change your privacy setting in MyAccount, or please send an e-mail to [theteam@cleeng.com](mailto:theteam@cleeng.com) subject “Unsubscribe”

Note: if you have Questions regarding the Cleeng Privacy Policy, we are pleased to answer them. Your questions to can be directed to [theteam@cleeng.com](mailto:theteam@cleeng.com). The most recent version of the Cleeng Privacy Policy can be found on this page.

By agreeing to the Cleeng User Agreement and/or the Cleeng Publisher Agreement you agree with the use of your personal information and data in accordance with the Cleeng Privacy Policy.

Last version : 18 February 2014
